greenfingers.com 2013-06-01

# Privacy Policy

|  | 

The following is for guidance only and does not affect the [Terms and Conditions](http://www.greenfingers.com/bottommenu.asp?subcategoryid=46). 

Greenfingers.com is committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect about you to administer your account, promote goods and services to you, and for market research purposes. We are committed to keeping your confidential information exactly that - confidential.

Please read on for more details about our privacy policy. 

**1\. What information do we collect?**

> When you register with Greenfingers.com we will collect your e-mail address. We may also keep a record of which products and services you are interested in. We also monitor traffic patterns and site use.
> 
> When you order, we need to know your name, e-mail address, delivery address, credit or debit card number and expiry date. This enables us to process and fulfil your orders and to notify you in the event of any queries.
> 
> We also request your telephone number, which allows us to contact you urgently if there is a problem with your order and allow couriers to contact you if problems arise with delivery. We will communicate with you by e-mail, telephone or letter.
> 
> When you enter a competition or prize draw, we may ask for your name, address, and e-mail address so that we can administer the contest and notify winners. We may also ask for further information for our marketing records.

**2\. How do we use the information?**

> At Greenfingers the information we collect about you is to make sure that the information or offers that we send you are relevant to you - we don't want to waste your time by sending you information or offers which you will not find interesting.
> 
> We may use the information we collect to occasionally notify you about important functionality changes to our web site, new Greenfingers.com services and special offers.
> 
> We do not pass on your details without your permission to anyone else unless it is in relation to services you have used through the site.
> 
> We will not sell, rent, share, trade or give away without your permission any information we hold about you.
> 
> From time to time, Greenfingers or other carefully selected companies that we have chosen may contact you with offers that may be of interest to you. If you do not wish to receive such offers, then please send an exact copy of your name and address to Greenfingers Trading Ltd Data Protection Department, Freepost SCO 7517, Livingston EH54 0BR. 
> 
> If you do not want to receive such offers or to be contacted by us by telephone, please uncheck the box in the registration section when you register. If you don't uncheck the box but decide later that you don't want to receive any more information just let us know by e-mailing us at [ unsubscribe@greenfingers.com ](mailto:unsubscribe@greenfingers.com)

**3 Further information**

> We would also like to send you useful and personalised gardening information and advice as well as details of special offers. You can choose to unsubscribe from newsletters at any time in future.
> 
> If you are unhappy to receive these mailings from us please let us know by e-mailing us at [ unsubscribe@greenfingers.com.](mailto:unsubscribe@greenfingers.com)

**4\. Your rights**

> You have a right to ask for a copy of the information we hold on you and to have any inaccuracies corrected

**5\. Your consent**

> By using our Site, you consent to the collection, processing and use of this information by Greenfingers.com.

**6\. Changes**

> Any changes to our privacy policy will be posted on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it.

**7\. Liability**

> We cannot be held liable for any loss that you may suffer if a third party obtains unauthorised access to any data, includingaccount details or details you provide us when accessing or ordering from this site, unless this can be proven at law to be due to our negligence.

**8\. Cookies**

> We do use 'cookies' which are small pieces of information that are stored on your computer's hard drive by your browser. These allow Greenfingers.com torecognise you and to provide features to make your use of the Site easier. Most browsers allow the cookie funciton to be turned off. If you want to know how to do this look at the help menu on your browser or contact our customer services on customerservices@greenfingers.com, or telephone them on 0845 345 0728.

**9\. In Summary**

> We are completely committed to protecting your privacy. If you have any comments or queries about our privacy policy, please e-mail us at [customer.services@greenfingers.com](mailto:customer.services@greenfingers.com) as we value your opinions.

**10\. Further information**

> For further information regarding all aspects of Greenfingers.com's contracts with customers please see our full [Terms and Conditions](http://www.greenfingers.com/bottommenu.asp?subcategoryid=46).

| **Other Terms And conditions Articles**  
---  
   Our Guarantee |      |     Privacy Policy  
   Returns And Refunds |      |     Secure Payment  
   Store Security |      |     Terms and Conditions  
  
|    
  
|   
---  
| To be notified of exclusive offers  
 **Follow Us On:** | [](http://www.facebook.com/greenfingerscom) |  | [](http://twitter.com/greenfingerscom) |   
  
OUR DEAL OF THE WEEK   
---  
HURRY THESE DEALS DON’T LAST LONG!   
  
 SAVE   
57%  
  
---  
| Usual Price 299.99 |  This Week Only  
129.99  
---|---  

The UK's favourite   
online garden store  
---  

Phone Calls Welcome!  
---  
|   
---  
|  **0845 345 0728**  
We are happy to answer any questions you may have during office hours.   
Bulk discounts available.
